<resources>
    <!--  Data in first layer-->
    <!-- Home -->
    <string name="app_name">SalonSculp</string>
    <string name="button_1">Make Up</string>
    <string name="button_2">Pre-Bride Service</string>
    <string name="button_3">Facials &amp; Skin Treatments</string>
    <string name="button_4">Body Spa &amp; D-tan</string>
    <string name="button_5">Hair Care &amp; Treatments</string>
    <string name="button_6">Manicure &amp; Pedicure</string>
    <string name="button_7">Gallery</string>


    <string name="content_description">Button</string>

    <!-- Data in second layer-->


    <!--  Make up-->

    <string name="Makeupinfo">At <b>Salonsculp makeup &amp; Spa</b>, we are not just a makeup service; we are your partners in enhancing your natural beauty
        and  elevating your confidence. Our dedication to excellence and unwavering passion for the art of makeup sets us
        apart as a leader in the industry.
    </string>

    <string name="Makeupinfo2"><b>Let\'s Begin Your Bridal Beauty Journey:</b></string>

    <string name="Makeupinfo3">Embark on a bridal beauty experience that\'s as unforgettable as your love story. Contact us today to schedule a
        consultation and take the first step towards achieving the bridal look you\'ve always dreamed of.
        Your love story is unique, and your bridal makeup should be too. Trust AMS to create a look that captures the
        essence of your love and radiates your inner beauty.</string>
    <string name="Makeupinfo4"><b>Feel free to customize this description to match your bridal makeup services, style, and business values. Make
        sure  to emphasize the  personalized approach, attention to detail, and the emotional significance of your role in  a  bride\'s special day.</b>
    </string>


    <!-- Pre-bride service  -->
    <string name="Prebrideinfo"><b>Pre-bride services</b> refer to a range of beauty and grooming treatments and services that
        are typically offered to brides
        in the period leading up to their wedding day.
        These services are designed to help the bride look and feel her best on her special day.
        Pre-bride services can include various beauty treatments, skincare regimens, and more.</string>

    <string name="Prebrideinfo2"><b>Here are some common pre-bride services packages designed for brides:</b></string>

    <string name="Prebrideinfo3"><b>Silver Pre-Bride Package         Rs.14999*</b></string>

    <string name="Prebrideinfo4">Threading, Body Regular Wax, Cleanup, Bleach, Facial, Manicure, Pedicure, Hair Spa, Body Spa, Mehandi (Hair),
        Haircut, Hairstyle, Saree Draping, Bridal Makeup.</string>

    <string name="Prebrideinfo5"><b>Gold Pre-Bride Package                    Rs.19999*</b></string>
    <string name="Prebrideinfo6">Threading, Body Cream Wax, Cleanup, Cheryls Bleach, Cheryls Facial, Manicure, Pedicure, Hair Spa, Body Spa,
        Body Polishing,
        Hair Colour, Haircut, Hairstyle, Saree Draping, Bridal Makeup.</string>

    <string name="Prebrideinfo7"><b>Platinum Pre-Bride Package                  Rs.25999*</b></string>
    <string name="Prebrideinfo8">Threading, Body Roll on Wax, Cleanup, O3+ Bleach, O3+ Facial, Adv. Manicure, Adv. Pedicure,
        Body Spa with Steam Bath, Body Polishing, Keratin Hair Spa,
        Fashion Hair Colour, Haircut, Hairstyle, Saree Draping, Haldi Makeup, Bridal Makeup.</string>

    <!--  Facial and Skin treatment  -->
    <string name="Facialinfo"><b>Facial and skin treatments</b> encompass a wide range of procedures and therapies
        designed to improve the health,
        appearance, and condition of the skin.
</string>
    <string name="Facialinfo2">ac</string>


    <!--  Body spa and D-tan  -->
    <string name="Bodyspainfo">A <b>Body Spa and D-Tan</b>, commonly referred to as a "spa and tan" experience,
        typically involve two distinct components: spa treatments focused on relaxation and pampering,
        and sunbathing or tanning to achieve a bronzed skin tone.
    </string>
    <string name="Bodyspainfo2">It\'s important to approach tanning, whether natural or artificial,
        with caution and to take measures to protect your skin from UV damage. Sunscreen and moderation are key.
        Skin health and safety should be a top priority when considering any type of tanning.
    </string>




<!--    Hare care and Treatments-->

    <string name="Hareinfo"><b>Hair care and treatment</b> are vital aspects of self-care, encompassing practices like regular washing, conditioning, and tailored trims. Using suitable products,
        such as mild shampoos and conditioners, helps maintain a healthy balance without stripping natural oils. Deep conditioning treatments and protective measures with heat protectants
        and UV-blocking products further contribute to overall hair well-being. Adopting a nutrient-rich diet and minimizing exposure to harsh chemicals are
        integral components of an effective hair care routine.
    </string>

    <string name="Hareinfo2">Healthy hair is crucial for both appearance and overall well-being. Regular trims prevent damage, promoting sustained growth,
        while adequate moisture and protection boost confidence and self-esteem.
        Incorporating thoughtful hair care practices into your overall self-care routine is essential.
    </string>

    <!--  Manicure and Pedicure  -->
    <string name="Manicureinfo">A <b>Manicure</b> is a beauty treatment that focuses on the care and grooming of the fingernails and hands.
        It involves various steps to clean, shape,
        and enhance the nails and surrounding skin, resulting in well-groomed and attractive hands.
    </string>


    <string name="Manicureinfo2">A <b>Pedicure</b> is a cosmetic beauty treatment for the feet and toenails.
        It is a relaxing and pampering experience that not only helps improve the appearance of
        the feet but also promotes foot health and hygiene.
    </string>


    <!--the data in third layer-->

    <!--Bridal Makeup -->
    <string name="Bridalinfo"><b>Elegant Bridal Beauty: Your Radiance, Our Expertise</b> </string>

    <string name="Bridalinfo2">Your wedding day is a cherished memory in the making, and at Anvi Makeover &amp; Spa,
        we are honored to be part of your journey towards a picture-perfect moment.
        Our bridal makeup services are designed to make you feel like the most beautiful version of yourself as you walk down the aisle.</string>

    <string name="Bridalinfo3"><b>Our Approach: Timeless Elegance, Bespoke Beauty, Flawless
        Execution, Stress-Free Experience, Radiant Glow:</b></string>

    <string name="Bridalinfo4"><b>Why Choose Us?</b></string>

    <string name="Bridalinfo5">Our passion for creating bridal beauty extends beyond makeup application.
        We\'re dedicated to making you feel confident, comfortable, and utterly breathtaking on your wedding day.
        It\'s not just about makeup; it\'s about embracing your moment in the spotlight with grace and poise.
    </string>

    <string name="Bridalinfo6"><b>Range Starts from: Rs. 8,000/-* to Rs. 15,000/-* (its vary on demand)</b>

    </string>


    <!--Engagement &amp; Reception Makeup-->
    <string name="Engagementinfo"><b>Captivating Engagement &amp; Reception Makeup: Unveiling Your
        Radiant Love</b>
    </string>

    <string name="Engagementinfo2">As you step into this beautiful chapter of your love story, let Anvi Makeover &amp;
        Spa, be your partner in enhancing your natural beauty and infusing your
        engagement day with enchantment. Our engagement makeup services are
        meticulously designed to complement your joy and create a look that embodies
        the love you share.
    </string>

    <string name="Engagementinfo3"><b>Our Approach: Romantic Glamour, Personalized Elegance, Effortless Radiance,
        Attention to Detail, Expressive Confidence</b>
    </string>

    <string name="Engagementinfo4"><b>Why Choose Us?</b></string>

    <string name="Engagementinfo5">We understand that your engagement day is a preview of the journey ahead. Our passion lies
        in crafting makeup looks that not only enhance your external beauty but also capture the
        magic of your emotions. We are dedicated to making you feel stunning, empowered, and
        deeply connected to the moment.</string>
    <string name="Engagementinfo6"><b>Range Starts from: Rs. 6,000/-* to Rs. 15,000/-* (its vary on demand)</b></string>


    <!--Mehendi & Haldi Makeup   -->

    <string name="Mehandiinfo"><b>Mehndi and Haldi</b> are traditional pre-wedding ceremonies in India. These ceremonies involve applying natural ingredients to the bride
        as part of a ritual and celebration. Makeup services for Mehndi and Haldi ceremonies are designed to enhance the beauty of the
        bride and groom while keeping the look natural and in line with the cultural significance of these events.


    </string>

    <string name="Mehandiinfo2">    Mehndi and Haldi makeup services are an important part of the pre-wedding festivities,
        helping the bride look their best while respecting the cultural significance of these ceremonies. Makeup artists play a crucial role in
        ensuring that the makeup complements the overall theme and traditional elements of these events.
    </string>

    <string name="Mehandiinfo3"><b>Our Approach: Vibrant Grace, Cultural Chic, Sun-kissed Radiance, Detailed Intricacy, Confident Expression</b></string>
    <string name="Mehandiinfo4"><b>Why Choose Us?</b></string>
    <string name="Mehandiinfo5"> Choosing a makeup artist or a makeup service provider for Haldi and Mehandi makeup is a significant decision when planning pre-wedding ceremonies.
        Here are some compelling reasons why clients might choose our services:
        \n
        <b>Expertise in Cultural Traditions:,
        High-Quality Products:, Professional Portfolio, Hygiene and Cleanliness: , Competitive Pricing:, Availability and Flexibility: .</b>
    </string>
    <string name="Mehandiinfo6"><b>Range Starts from: Rs. 6,000/-* to Rs. 15,000/-* (its vary on demand)</b>
    </string>

    <!--Simple Makeup-->


    <string name="Simplemakeupinfo"><b>Simple makeup</b> services typically involve creating a natural,
        everyday look that enhances a person\'s features without appearing too heavy or
        dramatic. This type of makeup is often used to enhance a person\'s features without drastically altering their appearance.
        It is typically characterized by its subtlety and the use of light and neutral tones. Simple makeup services are commonly sought for everyday wear,
        work, casual outings, or occasions where a more natural and low-key look is desired. Here are some key features of simple makeup services:
    </string>


    <string name="Simplemakeupinfo2"><b>Natural Look: , Light Coverage:, Soft Eye Makeup, Light Lip Colors:, Minimal Use of False Eyelashes,
        Long-Lasting and Comfortable: , Quick Application: .</b>
    </string>

    <string name="Simplemakeupinfo3"><b>Why Choose Us?</b></string>

    <string name="Simplemakeupinfo4">Our passion for Simple beauty extends beyond makeup application.
        We\'re dedicated to making you feel confident, comfortable, and utterly breathtaking on normal days.
        It\'s not just about makeup; it\'s about embracing your moment in the spotlight with grace and poise.</string>

    <string name="Simplemakeupinfo5"><b>Range Starts from: Rs. 1,000/-* to Rs. 5,000/-* (its vary on demand)</b></string>


    <string name="about_us_welcome">Our mission is to provide high-quality salon services and make you look and feel your best. We are dedicated to excellence in customer service and continuously strive to improve and innovate.</string>

    <string name="about_us_experience">At our salon, we believe in creating a relaxing and enjoyable experience for our clients. Our skilled and experienced team of stylists and beauty professionals is committed to delivering personalized services tailored to your unique needs.</string>

    <string name="about_us_services">Whether you\'re looking for a trendy haircut, a rejuvenating facial, or a pampering spa treatment, we\'ve got you covered. Our goal is not only to enhance your outer beauty but also to boost your confidence and well-being.</string>

    <string name="about_us_thank_you">Thank you for choosing our salon! We look forward to serving you and providing an exceptional salon experience.</string>
    <string name="homenavigation">HomeNavigation</string>


    <string-array name="treatment_options">
        <item>Select Service </item>
        <item>Make Up</item>
        <item>Pre-Bride service</item>
        <item>Facial &amp; Skill Treatment </item>
        <item>Body Spa &amp; D-Tan </item>
        <item>Hair Care Treatment</item>
        <item>Manicure &amp; Padicure</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="time_options">
        <item>Select Time</item>
        <item>09:00 AM - 12:00 PM</item>
        <item>12:00 PM - 03:00 PM</item>
        <item>03:00 PM - 06:00 PM</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>